If our vote doesn't matter, why are whites trying so hard to take it away from us? Come on now. I
lived through the civil rights movement. We are not going back. Jim Crow part two ain't working
for me. So we are going back. We literally have already gone back. The Democrats have done nothing
to stop it because they are fake opposition. Also, this argument, I want to inform you,
there's a really very clear answer to what this is really about. They work so hard to give you
something to work hard at fighting for. That is an empty effort. Instead of using your energy
to make demands and actually fight for things that can actually bring about egalitarianism.
Look it up. The whole we fighting for a vote and the civil rights movement,
the civil rights movement was not solely about voting. The civil rights movement
the civil rights movement was about fighting for the 14th amendment to actually apply
the amendment that says that everybody who is a citizen of the United States has the same laws
that they are living by. That's not just about voting. That was about segregation. That was about
access to housing, etc. However, they have very successfully narrowed that focus to just be about
voting and to trick you into thinking that if you just vote, everything else will work out,
even though it's never, ever proven to be the case. They work so hard at this because by working so hard
at taking away your right to vote, they keep you engaged in the practice of futility instead of
in community in the practice of demanding, by any means necessary, equality.